Paul Henry Sheats Papers
Paul Henry Sheats Papers
- Organizational records
  - National Training Laboratories
    - Printed materials
      - Conference planning, 1940s-1950s (Box 22)
      - Informational papers, 1970s (Box 22)
      - Interpersonal Process of Self-Disclosure: It Takes Two to See One, by Samuel A. Culbert, 1967 (Box 22)
      - Framework for Examining Change, by Jack R. Gibb, 1961 (Box 22)
      - Midwest Group for Human Resources newsletter, 1968; 1969; v. 1, no. 1; v. 2, no. 2 (Box 22)
      - Network News, Apr 1969 (Box 22)
      - News and Reports, 1968; 1969; v. 2, no. 4; v. 3, no. 1-3 (Box 22)
      - Research Reprint Series, 1961-1962; no. 7, 9, 11 (Box 22)
      - Role Playing / Large Group Committee, 1940s-1960s (Box 22)
      - Selected Reading Series, 1961; no. 1-2 (Box 22)
      - Selected Reading Series, 1962; no. 5-6 (Box 23)
      - Social Change: Ideas and Applications, 1971; v. 1, no. 2 (Box 23)
      - Story of the Bethel Idea, by Stuart Chase, 1957 (Box 23)
      - Subscription Service, 1963-1964; no. 1-4 (Box 23)
    - University - NTL Relationship Meeting, Feb-Mar 1963 (Box 105)
  - National University Extension Association
    - Board of Directors meetings, 1960; 1962-1967; 10 folders (Box 107)
    - Committees
      - Ad Hoc Committee, Apr 1960 (Box 108)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Constitution Revision, Organization, Structure and Fee Modification ("Eddy Committee"), 1961-1967; 2 folders (Box 108)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Organizational Problems, 1963 (Box 108)
      - Ad Hoc Committee for the Study of the 1961 Position Paper and Future Directions of the Association, Meeting, 16-19 Jul 1967 (Box 108)
      - Committee on American Indian Affairs (Box 108)
      - Awards and Honors Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 108)
      - Business and Affairs Committee, 1962; 1964 (Box 108)
      - Committee on Community Organization, 1949; 1953-1954,; 1956,; 1969 (Box 23)
      - Discussion and Debate Materials Committee, 1961-1965 (Box 108)
      - Executive Committee, 1965-1967 (Box 108)
      - Extension Services for the Armed Forces Committee, 1963 (Box 108)
      - Finance Committee, 1962 (Box 108)
      - Governmental Relations Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 108)
      - Humanities Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 108)
      - Committee on Inter-Association Relationships, 1962-1964 (Box 108)
      - Inter-Organizational Cooperation Committee, 1962 (Box 108)
      - Nominating Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 108)
      - Professional Development Committee, 1962-1963; 1965 (Box 108)
      - Publications and Public Information Committee, 1963 (Box 108)
      - Committee on Reports, 1961 (Box 23)
      - Research Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 108)
      - Resolutions Committee, 1962; 1963 (Box 108)
      - Terminal Education Committee, 1962 (Box 108)
      - World Affairs Committee, 1960 (Box 23)
      - World Affairs Committee, 1962 (Box 108)
    - Community Development Division, 1965-1966 (Box 23)
    - National Teacher Training Institute, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Meetings
      - 43rd Annual, 1958 (Box 23)
      - 44th Annual, 1959 (Box 23)
      - 45th Annual, 1960 (Box 23)
      - 45th Annual (cont.), 1960 (Box 105)
      - 46th Annual, 1961
        - Organizational correspondence (Box 105)
        - General plans (Box 105)
        - Newspaper clippings (Box 105)
        - Speech (Box 105)
        - Reports (Box 105)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
      - 47th Annual, 1962
        - Organizational correspondence (Box 106)
        - General plans (Box 106)
        - Speeches (Box 106)
        - Reports (Box 106)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
      - 48th Annual, 1963
        - Organizational correspondence, 1961-1963; 4 folders (Box 106)
        - General plans (Box 106)
        - Reports (Box 106)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
      - 49th Annual, 1964 (Box 24)
      - 49th Annual, additional material, 1964 (Box 106)
      - 50th Annual, 1965
        - Correspondence, general plans, speech by Sheats (Box 106)
        - Publications (Box 106)
      - 51st Annual, 1966
        - Correspondence, general plans, reports (Box 107)
        - Publications (Box 107)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 24)
      - 52nd Annual, 1967 (Box 24)
      - 52nd Annual (cont.), 1967 (Box 107)
      - Preparation of Extension Leaders, 1947 (Box 24)
    - Printed materials
      - Studies in University Extension Education, 1944-1946; 1951,; 1953-1954; no. 2-4, 6, 9, 11
      - Miscellaneous, 1940s-1970s (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Division of Audio-Visual Communications, 1963-1965 (Box 109)
      - Division of Conferences and Institutes, 1962 (Box 109)
      - Division of Evening Colleges and Class Extension, 1962-1964; 2 folders (Box 109)
      - Institute on the Federal Legislative Process, 5 May 1961 (Box 109)
      - NUEA Work-Study Conference on New Educational Media, 28-29 Apr 1962 (Box 109)
      - NUEA - Speech Association of America, Joint Symposium, Dec 1962 (Box 109)
      - Position Paper, 1960-1962 (Box 109)
      - Correspondence and drafts, 1960; 1961-1962,; undated; 3 folders
  - Southern Regional Education Board, Adult Basic Education Staff Development Project, Southeastern Region
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 24)
    - Proposal - Teacher Training, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Graduate Program Reports, 1971 (Box 24)
    - Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 24)
    - Reports, 1970s (Box 25)
    - Reports (legal size), 1971 (Box 91)
    - State Reports, 1971 (Box 25)
    - Speech, October 18, 1971 (Box 25)
    - Meetings
      - Graduate Program Development, Jun 1970 (Box 25)
      - Graduate Program Development, Oct 1971 (Box 25)
      - Planning of In-Service Workshops, 1971
      - Regional meeting, 2d, 1970 (Box 25)
      - Regional meeting, 3rd, 1970 (Box 25)
      - Regional meeting, 4th, 1971 (Box 26)
      - Regional meeting, 5th, 1972 (Box 26)
      - Regional meeting, 6th, 1973 (Box 26)
  - Unesco
    - Correspondence, 1958-1962; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Meetings
      - Consultative Committee on Adult Education, 3d, 1951 (Box 26)
      - Consultative Committee on Adult Education, 4th, 1952 (Box 26)
      - Consultative Committee on Adult Education, 8th, 1956 (Box 26)
      - Consultative Committee on Adult Education, 9th, 1957 (Box 26)
      - Consultative Committee on Adult Education, 10th, 1959 (Box 26)
      - Experts on Research in Literacy, 1968 (Box 26)
      - General Conference, 7th, 1952 (Box 26)
      - General Conference, 7th (cont.), 1952 (Box 27)
      - General Conference, 11th, 1960 (Box 27)
      - International Advisory Committee for Out of School Education, 2d session, 1970 (Box 27)
      - International Committee for the Advancement of Adult Education, 1st session, 1961 (Box 27)
      - International Consultative Liaison Committee for Literacy, 2d session, 1968 (Box 27)
      - Media, 1959; 1961-1962 (Box 27)
      - Seminar on Methods and Techniques of Adult Education in International Organizations Concerned With Women's Interests, 1959 (Box 27)
      - United States National Commission, 5th, 1955 (Box 27)
      - United States National Commission, 8th, 1961 (Box 27)
      - United States National Commission, 13th, 1969 (Box 27)
      - World Conference on Adult Education, 1st, 1949 (Box 27)
      - World Conference on Adult Education, 2nd, 1960; 3 folders (Box 27)
      - World Conference on Adult Education, 3rd, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Printed materials
      - Adult Education Information Notes, 1973-1974; no. 1, 8 (Box 28)
      - Literacy: a Newsletter, 1969-1970, 1974 (Box 28)
      - Literacy, 1965-1971 (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1970s; 3 folders (Box 28)
  - University Council on Education for Public Responsibility
    - Annual Meeting, 1962 (Box 29)
    - Associate Members, 1963 (Box 29)
    - Associates (Deans and Directors), 1962 (Box 29)
    - Board of Directors, 1962 (Box 29)
    - Program Committee, 1962 (Box 29)
    - Program Planning Committee, 1962 (Box 29)
  - University of California Extension
    See also Personal files: University Extension
    - Academic Senate Committee, 1950s-1960s (Box 29)
    - Dean's Administrative Council, 1963 (Box 29)
    - University Extension Council, 1964-1967 (Box 29)
    - Academic Plans, 1950s-1960s (Box 29)
    - Annual Reports, 1962-1966 (Box 29)
    - Annual Reports, 1966-1969 (Box 30)
    - Community Seminar Program, 1964-1965 (Box 30)
    - Extension Reorganization, 1960-1963; v.1-2 (Box 30)
    - Meetings
      - Approaches to Desegregation: The Superintendent's Perspective, 1969 (Box 30)
      - Articulation Conference, 1961 (Box 30)
      - Conference on Poverty in America, 1965 (Box 30)
      - Conference on the Creative Person, 1961 (Box 30)
      - Economic Growth Symposium, 1964 (Box 31)
      - Fulbright Conference on American Higher Education, 1956-1957; 1962-1963; 4 folders (Box 31)
      - Planning Conferences and Workshops, 1955 (Box 31)
    - Memoranda, Grant and Contract, 1964-1967 (Box 31)
    - Programs, 1962-1963; 1966 (Box 32)
    - Reports, 1950s-1960s (Box 32)
    - Salary scales, 1965-1967 (Box 32)
    - Statistical summaries, 1964-1966 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous printed materials, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Western Center for Community Education and Development
      - Activity Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
      - Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
      - Western Center for Continuing Education in Hospitals and Related Health Institutions Regional Conference on Hospitalwide Education and Training, 1968 (Box 32)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, Department of Education
    - Committee on Changing Roles of Adolescents and Young Adults, 1972-1973 (Box 32)
    - National Conference on Community Continuing Education, 1973 (Box 32)
    - Miscellaneous printed materials, 1953; 1971,; 1974 (Box 32)
  - Western Training Laboratory
    - Correspondence, administrative, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, staff, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - Design papers, 1960s (Box 33)
    - Group Development meetings, 1st through 5th, 1952-1956; 5 folders (Box 33)
    - Rosters, 1969 (Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous Papers, 1960s (Box 33)
  - Youth Opportunity Board of Greater Los Angeles
    - Community Development Evaluation Panel, 1965 (Box 34)
    - Progress reports, 1965 (Box 34)
- Meetings files
  - Adult Education Association of Michigan
    - Annual, 1966 (Box 34)
  - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A.
    - A.I.D. Conference, 1964 (Box 34)
    - Allerton Park Conference of Professors of Adult Education, 1955 (Box 34)
    - Delegate Assembly, 1973 (Box 34)
    - 18th Annual, 1968 (Box 34)
    - National Conference, 1971 (Box 34)
    - National Conference, speech research, 1971 (Box 34)
    - National Conference, 1974 (Box 34)
  - Agency for International Development
    - Adult Education in Developing Nations, 1962 (Box 34)
    - Conference on Multidisciplinary Analyses of Alternatives to Traditional Education in Latin America, 1973 (Box 34)
  - American Association of Junior Colleges
    - Committee on Continuing Education, 1966 (Box 34)
  - American Educational Research Association
    - Annual meetings, 1972; 1974,; 1975; 3 folders (Box 35)
  - American Hospital Association
    - Workshop on International Classification of Diseases, Adapted for Use in the United States (ICDA-8), 1969 (Box 35)
  - American National Red Cross
    - National Convention, 1972 (Box 35)
  - Association of Higher Education
    - 18th Annual meeting, 1963 (Box 35)
  - California Community College Continuing Education Association
    - 1st Annual meeting, 1970 (Box 35)
  - California Council on Adult Education
    - Annual meeting, 1969 (Box 35)
  - California State Department of Education
    - Conference on Vocational Education, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Santa Barbara Workshop in Adult Education, 1958; 1960; 2 folders (Box 35)
  - Commission of Professors of Adult Education
    - Ann Arbor Conference, 1957 (Box 35)
    - Madison Conference, 1959 (Box 36)
    - East Lansing Conference, 1960 (Box 36)
    - Philadelphia Conference, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Committee of Adult Education Organizations
    - Wingspread, 1969 (Box 36)
  - Community Development Society
    - 5th Annual, 1973 (Box 36)
  - Ford Foundation
    - Urban Extension Conference, 1963 (Box 36)
  - Galaxy Conference, 1969 (Box 36)
  - Hawaii State Department of Education
    - State Conference, 1963 (Box 36)
  - Highlander Research and Education Center
    - 1st Inter-American Adult Education Seminar, 1962 (Box 36)
  - Institute of Lifetime Learning
    - Institute Day, 1967 (Box 36)
  - International Congress of University Adult Education
    - World Conference, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Los Angeles Junior High School Principals Association
    - Improving Faculty Meetings, 1974 (Box 36)
  - Michigan State University, Kellogg Center for Continuing Education
    - 9th Annual meeting, 1966 (Box 37)
    - 11th Annual meeting, 1968 (Box 37)
  - National Association of Adult Educators
    - Extraordinary Congress, 1969 (Box 91)
  - National Association for Public School Adult Education
    - Ad Hoc Committee on a Professional Development Program for Public School Adult Educators, 1969 (Box 37)
    - International Conference, 17th annual, 1968 (Box 37)
  - National Institute of Mental Health
    - National Conference on Continuing Education, 1967 (Box 37)
  - New York University
    - 40th Anniversary of School of Continuing Education, 1975 (Box 37)
  - North American Conference on Adult Education
    - 1st meeting, 1967 (Box 37)
  - Pennsylvania State College
    - J. Orvis Keller Building Dedication, 1966 (Box 37)
  - Purdue University
    - Albert P. Marble and Midland-Ross Foundation Lecture in Continuing Education, 1966 (Box 37)
  - Rutgers State University
    - Interuniversity Seminar on Urban Extension, 1966 (Box 37)
  - Santa Barbara City College
    - 50th Anniversary, 1969 (Box 37)
  - Syracuse University
    - Psychological Backgrounds of Adult Education, 1962 (Box 37)
    - Sociological Backgrounds of Adult Education, 1963 (Box 38)
    - University in Urban Society, 1966 (Box 38)
  - Texas Christian University
    - Fort Worth Week - Community and University, 1969 (Box 38)
  - United States Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 38)
    - Ideals of American Freedom and the International Dimensions of Education, 1962 (Box 38)
  - United States International Cooperation
    - Administration - Korea (Box 38)
    - Inter-Regional Conference on Community Development and its Role in Nation Building, 1961 (Box 38)
  - University of Akron
    - 50th Anniversary, 1966 (Box 38)
  - University of Alberta
    - Conference on Post Secondary and Continuing Education, 1966 (Box 38)
  - University of California - San Francisco Medical Center
    - Storage of Abilities: A Centennial Celebration, 1968 (Box 38)
  - University of Chicago
    - Application of Adult Education Concepts, 1972 (Box 38)
    - Workshop for Administrators of University Adult Education, 1966; 1968; 2 folders (Box 38)
  - University of Maryland
    - 4th World-Wide Armed Forces Education Conference, 1962 (Box 38)
  - University of Pittsburgh, School of General Studies
    - Board of Visitors, 1973 (Box 38)
  - University of Tennessee
    - Conference on Higher Adult Education in the South, 1961 (Box 38)
  - Utah
    - Governor's Conference, 1965 (Box 38)
  - Utah State University
    - Conference on Higher Education, 1965 (Box 38)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education
    - Annual, 1964 (Box 39)
    - Western Regional Conference on Education Beyond the High School, 1957 (Box 39)
  - World Confederation of Organizations of the Teaching Profession
    - Annual Meeting, 1961 (Box 108)
    - General Assembly, 10th (Box 39)
    - General Correspondence, 1959-1960; 1961 (Box 108)
    - International Conference on Adult Education, 1st, 1959 (Box 108)
    - International Conference on Adult Education, 2nd, 1961 (Box 39)
    - International Conference on Adult Education, 3rd, 1962 (Box 39)
    - Seminar, 5th, 1970 (Box 39)
    - Seminar, 6th, 1971 (Box 39)
    - Seminar, 8th, 1973 (Box 39)
- Subject files
  - Administration, 1960s-1970s (Box 39)
  - Adult Basic Education
    See also Subject files: Teacher training.
    - Alabama State University, 1970s; 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Appalachian Adult Basic Education Demonstration Center, 1969 (Box 40)
    - Appalachian Adult Education Center, 1970s (Box 40)
    - California, 1960s-1970s (Box 40)
    - Columbia University, 1970 (Box 40)
    - ERIC Clearinghouse on Adult Education, 1968 (Box 40)
    - Florida State University, 1968; 3 folders (Box 40, 41)
    - Illinois, 1965 (Box 41)
    - Indiana University, 1970 (Box 41)
    - National Advisory Committee on Adult Basic Education, 1968 (Box 41)
    - National Multimedia Center for Adult Basic Education
      - Cross-referenced index for abstracts, 4 folders (Box 93)
      - Abstracts, 000189, 000193-000195, 000598, 000701-000800, 000901, 001000-001600 (Box 93)
      - Abstracts, 001601-002500 (Box 94)
      - Abstracts, 002601-003100 (Box 95)
    - National Association for Public School Adult Education, circa 1965 (Box 41)
    - National University Extension Association, 1966-1968; 4 folders (Box 41)
    - Nevada, 1969-1970 (Box 42)
    - North Carolina State University, 1960s-1970s (Box 42)
    - Northern Illinois University, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Ohio State Board of Education, 1967 (Box 42)
    - Ohio State University, 1967-1969; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - University of Chicago, 1971 (Box 42)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1970 (Box 42)
    - University of Missouri, 1972 (Box 43)
    - University of Washington, 1965 (Box 43)
    - White Plains Adult Education Center, 1973 (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 43)
  - Aged
    - Bibliographies (Box 43)
    - California Governor's Conference on Aging, 1951; 1960,; 1967; 3 folders (Box 43)
    - Conferences, 1950s-1960s (Box 44)
    - Florida State University Leadership Development Institute, 1969; 1971,; 1972 (Box 44)
    - Guideposts to Effective Action in Aging, 1960; Case Study, no. 1, 3, 6-10 (Box 44)
    - Ohio State University, 1964 (Box 44)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1950s-1960s (Box 44)
    - Older Workers, 1950s (Box 45)
    - University of Chicago, 1961 (Box 45)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1961; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 45)
  - Behavioral Science, 1940s; 1960s-1970s (Box 45)
  - Civic Education, 1939; 1950s-1960s; 3 folders (Box 45, 46)
  - Community Development
    - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. (Box 46)
    - Agency for International Development, 1950s-1960s (Box 46)
    - American Association of Junior Colleges, 1960s (Box 46)
    - American Council for the Community, 1951-1952 (Box 46)
    - Association for the Study of Community Organization, 1960s (Box 46)
    - Cerritos College, 1974-1975 (Box 46)
    - Colorado State University, 1971-1973; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Columbia University Teachers College, 1949 (Box 47)
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1960s-1970s (Box 47)
    - Community Action Program, 1960s (Box 47)
    - Community Development Review, 1956-1963; no. 3; no. 6; v. 4, no. 1-4; v. 5, no. 1-4; v. 6, no. 1-3; v. 7, no. 1; v. 8, no. 1 (Box 47)
    - Community Service News, 1945; 1947; v. 3, no. 3; v. 5, no. 3, 5; (Box 47)
    - Community Service News, 1949-1951; v. 7, no. 3-5; v. 8, no. 3; v. 9, no. 4 (Box 48)
    - Earlham College Community Dynamics Annual Reports, 1948-1951; 1953 (Box 48)
    - Earlham College, miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 48)
    - Economically Disadvantaged, 1960s-1970s (Box 48)
    - General Federation of Women's Clubs, 1950s-1960s (Box 48)
    - Indiana University - Purdue University, 1950s-1960s; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - International, 1958 (Box 48)
    - Michigan State University, 1950s (Box 48)
    - Mississippi State University, 1950s-1960s (Box 48)
    - Montana State University, 1950s (Box 48)
    - New York State Citizens' Council, 1956 (Box 48)
    - New York University, 1954 (Box 49)
    - Northern Illinois University, 1967 (Box 49)
    - San Bernardino Valley College, 1950s (Box 49)
    - Southern Illinois University, 1950s-1970s; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Texas Technological College, 1957 (Box 49)
    - United Nations, 1950s-1960s (Box 49)
    - University of California Extension, 1950s-1960s (Box 50)
    - University of Kentucky, 1950s (Box 50)
    - University of Michigan, 1950s (Box 50)
    - University of Virginia, 1940s (Box 50)
    - University of Washington, 1950s-1960s (Box 50)
    - University of Wisconsin, 1969 (Box 50)
    - Washington University, 1960s (Box 50)
    - Wayne State University, 1960s (Box 50)
    - West Georgia College, 1960s-1970s (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930s-1950s (Box 50)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s; 3 folders (Box 51)
  - Community Education, 1940s (Box 51)
  - Consumer Education, 1969; bibliography; miscellaneous; 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Counseling, 1960s (Box 51)
  - Curriculum, 1958 (Box 51)
  - Developing Countries
    - Bibliography, 1965 (Box 51)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 52)
  - Evaluation, 1950s-1970s (Box 52)
  - Family, 1940s-1960s (Box 52)
  - Finance, 1930s-1960s; 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Goals, 1960s (Box 52)
  - Graduate programs, 1950s-1970s (Box 52)
  - Graduate programs, 1950s-1970s (Box 53)
  - Group dynamics discussion leadership
    - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A.
      - Leader's Digest, 1950s; v. 1, 2 (Box 53)
      - Leadership Pamphlets, 1955-1957; no. 2, 3, 5, 7 (Box 53)
    - Autonomous Groups Bulletin, 1945-1953; v. 1, no. 1-3; v. 2, no. 2, 4; v. 3, no. 4; v. 4, no. 1-4; v. 5, no. 1-4; v. 6, no. 1-4; v. 7, no. 1-4; v. 8, no. 1-3; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - Autonomous Groups Bulletin, 1953-1957; 1960; v. 8, no. 4; v. 9, no. 1-4; v. 10, no. 1, 2, 4; v. 11, no. 2-4; v. 12, no. 1, 3, 4; v. 15, no. 3, 4; 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Leadership Resources Inc.
      - Bibliographies, 1968 (Box 54)
      - Learning About Leadership Series, 1961 (Box 54)
      - Looking into Leadership, 1961 (Box 54)
      - Management series, 1968 (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930s-1940s; 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s; 5 folders (Box 55)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s; 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 56)
  - History, 1930s-1940s; 1960s (Box 56)
  - Industry, 1950s-1960s (Box 56)
  - Innovation, 1960s-1970s (Box 56)
  - Labor education, 1950s (Box 56)
    See also Subject files: Vocational education
  - Labor education, 1960s-1970s (Box 57)
  - Learning, 1950s-1970s (Box 57)
  - Liberal education
    - Fund for Adult Education
      - Lectures, 1950s (Box 57)
      - Occasional Papers, 1950s; no. 1-3 (Box 57)
      - Reports, 1950s-1960s (Box 57)
      - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 57)
  - Libraries, 1950 (Box 57)
  - Lifelong Learning, 1970s (Box 57)
  - Literacy
    - International Institute for Adult Literacy Methods
      - Literacy Discussion, 1971; v. 2, no. 1 (Box 57)
      - Literacy Documentation, 1972; v. 1, no. 3-4 (Box 58)
      - Literacy Work, 1972; 1974; v. 1, no. 5; v. 3, no. 4 (Box 58)
      - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 58)
    - Puerto Rico, 1955 (Box 58)
    - World Education Inc., 1971 (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970s (Box 59)
  - Mass media
    - Mass Media/Adult Education, pubilshed by Adult Education Association of the U.S.A., 1967-1969; nos. 1-10, 23 (Box 59)
    - Television
      - Chicago Junior City College, 1950s-1960s (Box 59)
      - Juvenile Delinquency, 1964 (Box 59)
      - Rural Family Development, 1970s (Box 59)
      - University Council on Education for Public Responsibility, 1966 (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s (Box 60)
  - Methodology, 1940s-1960s (Box 60)
  - Minorities, 1960s-1970s (Box 60)
  - Open University
    - Wisconsin, 1970s (Box 60)
    - Miscellaneous, 1960s-1970s (Box 60)